seoegghead.com 2015-12-30

# Privacy Policy & Terms of Use » SEO Egghead

## Privacy Policy & Terms of Use

## Our Commitment

We have created this privacy statement to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy. This page discloses our various information gathering and dissemination practices and policies. 

## Automatic Information Logging

This web site uses web analytics and other reporting tools to help analyze how users use our site. These tools use cookies, which are text files placed on your computer, to help collect standard internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form. The information generated with the cookie about your use of the website, including your IP address, is transmitted to various vendors. This information is then used to compile statistical reports on website activity to improve the web site. We will never (and will not allow any third party) track or collect any personally identifiable information for visitors to our site. Our web analytics vendors do not associate your IP address with any other data held by them. Neither we nor the web analytics vendors will seek to link an IP address with the identity of a computer user. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any personally identifying information from any source, unless you explicitly submit that information via a form on our website. 

## Disabling Cookies

You may configure your browser to decline cookies to disable information logging. 

## External Links

This site contains links to other sites. SEO Egghead Inc. and its authors are not responsible for the privacy practices or any content on such referenced web sites. 

## Personal Information

When you comment, subscribe, or sign up for an email list, we ask for your email address. This information may be used by us to contact you. Your personal information will not be distributed to anyone for any purpose. 

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We use Verisign's Malware Scan to scan our web site at interval for any malware. 

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the practices of this site, you may contact us.
